{
    "id": "50c8611f13dd4a5395d00f25a51b6a83",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "As there was no ............................ in waiting, we left.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worth",
                "use",
                "point",
                "time"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ba3a5d5adc64aaeb1ae3b970c6c1b5f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The storm played havoc .............................. our flight schedules.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'play havoc with'.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c165a2b243a421e92daa6b3871c68c8"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................ all I know, she is still married to him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "For",
                "Much",
                "Far"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d09788a11af84c00a2d91b2d57e81a2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward .............................. you.",
            "description": "After 'look forward', we use 'to + ing form'.",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "to seeing",
                "for seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b90cb323f72a4240a43a61f85dd6c3a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Didn't I tell you .............................. it?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not touching",
                "not to touch",
                "for not touching"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "138481f33c0943d39e6ef2c1bd5d1fe0"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................... the time we reached there, they had finished.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'by the time'.",
            "answers": [
                "By",
                "Within",
                "For",
                "In"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "add770897748483cb298c83f30f642ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will have to take the stairs because the lift is ...........................",
            "description": "When things are out of door, they don't work.",
            "answers": [
                "out of shape",
                "out of order",
                "out of condition"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "220158cf072640c69896a2816761e0c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ............................ better pay the fee today to avoid late payment charges.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'had better'. It is used to give strong advice. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8caab8c2db9a4fff9fe0dfdc8ddca19f"
        },
        {
            "question": "His electricity was ........................... off because he hadn't paid the bill.",
            "description": "To cut off is to stop the supply of something.",
            "answers": [
                "taken",
                "cut",
                "broken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f859116e0db495fabedf2b92226bb0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ............................. tears when I told her that she had failed her exam.",
            "description": "To burst into tears is to start crying.",
            "answers": [
                "broke into",
                "burst into",
                "burst out",
                "broke down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60fca63dbca74f6e9a2196054d60b504"
        },
        {
            "question": "The plane departed on time .............................. the fog.",
            "description": "In spite of is the correct expression. Despite and in spite of mean the same and are both possible here. Even though is a conjunction and should be followed by a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "in spite",
                "despite",
                "despite of",
                "even though"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f0175bd53ae4aa4ae8802fc694c78ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chimneys ........................ too much smoke.",
            "description": "To give off is to send out.",
            "answers": [
                "give in",
                "give up",
                "give off",
                "give over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1af8490f0576449a974f1f3d7413b2da"
        }
    ]
}